Guide to the Nathaniel Kleitman Papers 1896-2001
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Oversized Materials
  - Research and writing, bibliographic card catalog, index cards, K-M, undated (Box 43)
  - Research and writing, bibliographic card catalog, index cards, M-Z, undated (Box 44)
  - Research and writing, name index, index cards, undated (Box 45)
  - Research and writing, reprint requests, postcards, 1945-1978 (Box 46)
  - Print publications, articles on Kleitman and other sleep experiments, newspaper and magazine clippings, 1938-1951 (Box 47)
  - Print publications, magazines containing sleep articles, 1932-1966 (Box 48)
  - Print publications, sleep references in articles, scrapbooks containing newspaper and magazine clippings, 1936-1941 (Box 49)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, 3 wooden boxes containing surgical tools, undated (Box 50)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, Counter Dot Photo Interpreter tool, undated (Box 50)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, pen light, undated (Box 50)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, unidentified geological samples, undated (Box 50)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, magnifying spectacles, undated (Box 50)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, goggles on wooden mount, undated (Box 51)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, award certificates and diplomas, 1919-1947 (Box 52)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, American Sleep Disorders Association Honorary Fellowship certificate, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, Distinguished Service Award of the Thomas W. Salmon Committee on Psychiatry and Mental Hygiene, certificate and correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, sleep posters, 1929-1951 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, Thames River Navy certificate, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, University of Chicago Alumni Association Professional Achievement Award, certificate, program, correspondence, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, University of Chicago Club of Greater Los Angeles Distinguished Alumnus Award, certificate and correspondence, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Audio visual and photographs, "We The People," Professor Kleitman spot, LP record, July 1st, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Audio visual and photographs, Time To Sleep, LP record and correspondence, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Artifacts and memorabilia, ammunition box, undated (Box 54)
  - Audio visual and photographs, data charts and figures, glass slides, undated (Box 54)